就在去年 12 月我开始静脉注射治疗之后
right after I started the IVs back in December
那就是全部，我是说我的大脑，它，它，它
was that all was I mean my brain was it it it
它，它，我，我，我觉得它变得更清晰了
it it I I I felt like it was clearer
就像思绪来得很轻松
like it was like thoughts came very easy
我不需要费力去想词儿了
I didn't have to search for words
我不需要费力去想名字了
I didn't have to search for names
我不需要费力去搜寻各种事情
I didn't have to search for different things
不再会想“那是什么？那叫什么来着？”
and go what was that what was that
真是太神奇了，在我接受了
I just it's amazing how clear after I
静脉注射 DMSO 之后，我的大脑再次变得如此清晰
got the ivdmso my brain was again
检查结束之后
after we got done with the exam
他看着我
he he he looked at me
他和我一起坐了下来
and he um he sat down with me
在检查完之后
and after the exam
他说道，“听着”
and he goes  look
我绝不会在病人第一次就诊时就告诉他们这些
I would never tell somebody this on their first visit
我认为你有运动神经元方面的问题
I think you have a motor neuron issue
嗯……而且我认为是肌萎缩侧索硬化症（ALS）
and um and I think it's ALS
尤其是去年冬天
and especially last winter
嗯，我的情况开始恶化，并且开始……
um I started going downhill and started
呼吸方面有很多问题，嗯，我当时
having a lot of breathing issues  um I was
呃，白天也会发生这种情况
uh it would happen during the day
但最严重的是在晚上
but the worst was at night
我会发现，嗯
where I would find that um
我的，呃，呼吸在半夜里
my uh breathing in the middle of the night
我一晚上会醒来 5
I'd wake up 5
10 次左右
10 times a night
感觉就像是，嗯
it seemed like um
处于完全的恐慌中，仿佛溺水了一样
in a complete panic as though I was drowning
好像我的横膈膜突然停止了工作
as if my diaphragm had just stopped
肺部也不再起伏了
and wasn't moving my lungs anymore
有时我不得不强迫自己
and at times I'd have to force myself
先呼气，然后才能吸气
to exhale before I could inhale
去年冬天，我以为自己
last winter I thought I was
实际上已经在走下坡路了
actually on the way downhill
事实上，我们当时甚至已经订购了轮椅
in fact we actually ordered a wheelchair
你有没有给动物进行过二甲基亚砜（DMSO）静脉注射？
do you ever use DMSO intravenously on an animal
她说，是的，我做过
and uh she said yes  uh I do
我问，那你会在什么情况下这样做？
and I said well when would you do that
她说，如果我有一只动物
and she said well if I had an animal
倒在地上起不来
that was down and couldn't get up
嗯，它有严重的神经系统问题
um  and it had a severe neurological problem
我就在那儿停了下来，心想
and I stopped it right there and I go
严重的神经系统问题
severe neurological problem
而且无法起身
and can't get up
我说那听起来非常像渐冻症（ALS）
I said that sounds an awful lot like ALS
她说，是的
and she says yeah
确实有点像
kind of does
我说，好吧
I said well
我说，所以你是通过静脉注射给药吗
I said so you give it intervinously
我问这管用吗
I said does it work
她回答说，管用
and she goes yeah
很多时候都管用
many times it does
很多时候我能让马重新站起来
many times I can get the horse up on its feet
或者让其他动物站起来
or the animal
我可以让它站起来，开始进行处理
I can get it on its feet and start working with it
并开始治疗它，我说，好吧
and start treating it  and I said  well
那太不可思议了，我说
that's amazing  I said
所以我们正将其用于治疗一种严重的神经系统
so we're using that for a severe neurological
导致动物无法站立的问题
problem on an animal that can't get up
但我们不是为了人类才这么做的
but we're not doing this for humans
她说是的
and she said yeah
所以我想，好吧
so I thought well
让我们试着把 DMSO 涂在我的脊柱上
let's try putting the DMSO on my spine
看看我的脊柱问题是否能
let's see if my spinal issues could
与这件事情有关
have something to do with with this
而我发现最令我惊讶的是
and the thing that I found that was amazing
在那样做之后的短短三天内，那些
was that within three days of doing that  those
呃，那种醒来时感觉像是在
uh  episodes of waking up like I was
溺水发作的情况就完全停止了
drowning completely stopped
我开始睡得更香了
I started sleeping better
我开始感觉好多了
I started feeling better
我的双臂开始恢复力量
I started getting strength back in my arms
我竟然能够把那些
I actually was able to pull the
桁架拉过马路，你知道的
trusses across the road  you know
就这样穿过马路走了 30 英尺
so 30 feet across the road
走到起重机可以吊起他的地方
to where the the the crane could pick him up
每一片桁架都重达 340 磅
and each of those trusses weighed 340 pounds
那天晚上我告诉我的妻子，我说
and I I told my wife that that night I'm like
我不敢相信，这是多年来第一次
I can't believe it's the first time in years that
我感觉到手臂的肌肉在正常运作
I felt my muscles work correctly in my arms
结果显示，我从原本整晚
it showed that I had gone from spending
90% 的时间血氧水平处于
90% of the night with my oxygen levels at
89% 或以下，下降到仅占整晚的 42%
89 or below to only 42% of the night
且最长持续发作时间也从原本的
and my longest episode had gone from
从 13 分钟减少到了 4 分钟
13 minutes down to four minutes
发作次数也大大减少了
and the number of episodes had greatly decreased
我在 10 月 31 日停止了使用二甲基亚砜（DMSO）
I stopped using the DMSO on October 31st
我没有告诉我的妻子
I didn't tell my wife
我没有告诉任何人我在做什么
I didn't tell anybody what I was doing
腿部和手臂的
the weakness in the legs and the
虚弱感开始再次出现
arms started coming back
我……我注意到我的耐力正在下降
I I s I noticed uh I was my endurance was dropping off
嗯……我当时完全没有精力
um  I I had I I just I had no energy
我的妻子，嗯，她走过来问我
my wife um she came up and asked me
她说，她说，托德
and she said she said Todd
看起来二甲基亚砜（DMSO）没起作用，而且，嗯
it doesn't seem like the the DMSO's working  and um
她接着说，你，你，你的情况不太好
she goes you you you're not doing well
我不明白在那期间发生了什么
I don't understand what happened within
就在使用 DMSO 后的最初 24 小时内
that first 24 hours after using the DMSO
我惊讶地发现自己感觉好多了
I was amazed at how much better I was feeling
在接下来的那一周里，情况开始
and then over the next week things just started it
变得越来越好，越来越好
kept getting better and better and better
在过去的 10 年里
for the past 10 years
我注意到的一件事是，当所有这些..
one of the things that I I I I noticed when all
这一切都始于我腿部出现的问题
this all started was the issues with my legs
它们感觉就像面条一样软弱无力
they felt like wet noodles
感觉完全没有力气
they felt like they didn't have strength
我管这叫我的“果冻腿”
and I I I called it my jelly legs
甚至还涂抹了外用二甲基亚砜 (DMSO)
even applying the topical DMSO
我的双腿发软感一直没消失，我是说
I never got rid of the jelly legs  I mean
虽然有所改善
there was improvements
但那种感觉始终还在
but I never got rid of it
嗯，但用了静脉注射 DMSO 后，这种感觉消失了
um but with the IV DMSO it went away
腿部感觉比过去 10 年里的任何时候都要强健有力
they felt stronger than they'd felt in 10 years
我坐在他的诊疗台上说，医生
and I sat down on his table and I said DOC
检查一下我的反射
check my reflexes
他看了看我，说“好吧”
he just looked at me and goes OK
他走过来
he walked over
检查了我的反射情况
and he checked the reflex at my
右膝盖，它几乎动不了
right knee and it barely moved
它已经好几年没那样动过了
it hasn't done that in years
他看着我说道，托德
and he looked at me and he goes Todd
那几乎和正常人一样了
that was almost normal
我无法用言语充分形容这种巨大的变化
I cannot describe enough the difference
昨天早上的状态
between the way I was yesterday morning
在我去输液之前
before I went and got the IV
还有昨天晚上
and then yesterday evening
甚至包括今天，嗯
and then even today  um
感觉头脑清醒了多少
in how how much clearer
我的大脑思维非常清晰，嗯
and articulate my brain is  um
这对我来说简直太不可思议了
it's it's it's amazing to me
真的，我感觉好多了
and and and literally how much better I feel
说话变得顺畅多了
how much better I can talk
呼吸也变得顺畅多了
how much better I can breathe
尤其是呼吸方面
especially the breathing